

Le Trung Minh

fullstack developer

PROFILE -

- **(**
- portfolio-minhle252s-
- **Q**.12

SKILLS .

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Proficient in programming languages: PHP, Nodejs, Javascript
- Experience with HTML5, SASS/CSS3, Reactjs, React native

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication skills, convey ideas, work content clearly, fully, concisely.
- Have a spirit of self-study, eager to learn related knowledge and issues
- Effective problem-solving skills

REFERENCES -

- · Name: Ho Doan Trung
- Position: Product owner,
 Executive director of fmax company

OBJECTIVE

Software engineer with over 2 years of experience in software development and commercial applications. I look forward to joining the company to build innovative and creative business solutions to increase revenue for the company. In my previous roles, I completed projects on time 98% of the time. At the same time, build important processes to increase efficiency and optimize project time.

WORK EXPERIENCE -

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

10/2023 - 08/2024

Fmax Company

Team size: 5

Technologies used:

- php(zend), mysql, javascript, React native, swift
- Link:

Responsibilities:

- Upgrading from B2C to B2B e-commerce system
- Participate and work with UI/UX, BA/PM team during requirements analysis.
- Maximize efficiency, data quality, scope, operability and flexibility of the application.
- Find and fix software errors (debugging)
- Modify, update, refactor and debug code
- Learn new technologies, techniques/Improve existing technologies in line with company goals/strategies

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

12/2022 - 10/2023

Fmax Company

Team size: 4

Technologies used:

- Php(zend), mysql, javascript, React native, swift
- Link:

Responsibilities:

- Participate in discussions with departments to clarify desires and provide solutions in line with the company's strategy
- Participate in upgrading the marketing toolkit (Product promotions, order promotions, promotional codes, flash sales)
- Build a CMS system for the website and ensure compatibility for the website and mobile app (do not use open source code)

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

06/2022 - NOW

Minh Thu Handmade

Team size: 3

Technologies used:

Language: nodejs(expressjs), typescript, reactjs, mysql, taiwincss

- · phone:
- Relation: He was my direct supervisor at Fmax
 Technologies where I worked on several high-profile projects. He can speak to my coding skills and project management abilities.
- Cloud: vps, linux(ubuntu)
- Link:

Responsibilities:

- Build an e-commerce website for the "Minh Thu handamde" store.
- For the user interface, use Vanilla JS and optimize the code from the built features, in addition to optimizing SEO efficiency in the project instead of focusing only on the features.
- Permissions
- Revenue Statistics
- Order Management
- News Management
- User Management
- Customer Management
- Product Management
- Category Management

EDUCATION -

INFOMATION TECHNOLOGY

2020 - 2022

Sai Gon College

Graduate with good degree